





### **Summary**

Jump to Section

A highly competent and results oriented L1 Support Engineer with 1+ years of experience in Network Planning Engineer, Networking, Data Structures, Network Support, Technical Support, Defect Tracking, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Edipse, Selenium

## **Work Experience**

ONE97 communication pvt ltd , as L1 support engineer -Networking Apr 2019 to Apr 2019

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

- PayTM as Associate Jan 2019 to Till Date
- Horizon service India Pvt Ltd as Associate Jan 2017 to Sep 2018

^ Back to Top

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Computers) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2015 PG: M.Tech (Computers) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2021

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:
Diploma in computer programming

^ Back to Top

#### **IT Skills**

ii Okiii3	
Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
RDBMS	
html ,javascript,css	
SELENIUM	
Redmine, Bugzilla 4.2.	

# 1

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Java,C++,J2EE	
Edipse ,Selenium IDE	
crucible	

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
English		✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.